Guide to the LAC0018 The James Neff Labor Archives - the IBT Collection, 1953-1989 LAC0018
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
LAC0018 The James Neff Labor Archives - the IBT Collection
1953-1989
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Neff, James
LAC0018
42 Linear Feet 42 record center cartons containing 1,428 microfilm reels, paper files, 142 VHS tapes, and photographs.
This collection consists of 14 series. Series 1 contains microfilm reels of a range of documentation created by various departments and offices of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The microfilm reels were selected for copying by James Neff in the 1990s. Series 2 contains files having to do with IBT history. Series 3 contains files having to do with IBT locals. Series 4 contains miscellaneous newspapers produced by IBT. Series 5 contains biographies and news clippings pertaining to certain key members of IBT. Series 6 contains articles, pamphlets, and flyers published by IBT. Series 7 contains files having to do with the Eastern Conference of Teamsters. Series 8 contains correspondence between IBT President Dan Tobin and US President Franklin Delano Roosevelt. Series 9 contains files having to do with various large companies associated with IBT. Series 10 contains newspaper clippings about IBT. Series 11 contains publications by organizations outside of IBT. Series 12 contains constitution booklets and convention materials from IBT and IBT affiliated groups. Series 13 contains VHS and U-Matic tapes of movies produced by IBT or related to IBT. Series 14 contains miscellaneous photographs from IBT.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
The microfilm collection is organized by IBT department or topics covered in the microfilmed documentation. Series 2 through 12 are organized chronologically and by subject. Series 13 is arranged in no particular order. Series 14 is arranged by photograph type.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of James Neff, 04-2016, 2016-103
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material pertaining to the International Brotherood of Teamsters amassed by board member and president of Investigative Reporters and Editors James Neff. Materials include microfilm reels, paper files, VHS and U-Matic tapes, photographs and transparency film slides dating from 1953-1989
Biographical / Historical
James Neff, born 1953, is a US Nonfiction author and an investigative journalist. Neff is an alumnus of the University of Notre Dame and holds a Master's Degree in American Civilization from the University of Texas Austin. He has worked as a reporter, columnist, editor, and investigator for a number of publications including the Austin-American Statesman, The Plain Dealer, The Seattle Times, The Philadelphia Inquirer, Philadelphia Daily News, and Philly.com. From 1994 to 1999, Neff was the Willard M. Kiplinger Chair in Public Affairs Reporting in Ohio State University School of Journalism and Communication. He was a board member and president of Investigative Reporters and Editors, Inc. from 1991 to 2002.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Publications; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; Neff, James; Hoffa, James R. (James Riddle)
- Administrative files, 1953-1989; Series 1; 25.5 Linear Feet Boxes 1-17, All Record Center Boxes
  Arrangement
  The Administrative files series is arranged numerically by reel number.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains documents that were originally housed in the IBT central files room and cover a range of topics.
  - Administrative Files 100s, 600s, and 1100s, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Files 1900s and 2000s, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Files 2900s and 3000s, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Files 3000s, 3100s, and 3800s, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 4)
  - Administrative Files 3900s and 4600s, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 5)
  - Administrative Files 4700s, A- Series, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 6)
  - A- Series and -A Series, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 7)
  - Legal Department (LE Series), 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 8)
    The Legal Department series is arranged numerically by reel number.
    The Legal Department series contains documents relating to IBT's legal concerns such as court cases.
  - Legal Department, Government Affairs, McClellan Hearings, and NLRB Files, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 9)
    The Government Affairs series, the McClellan Committee Hearings sries and tghe NLRB files series contain a range of documents related to these topics.
    These reels are arrannged numerically by reel number.
  - News Clips and Monitorships, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 10)
    The Newsclips series and Monitorships series are arranged numercially by reel number.
    The Newsclips series and the Monitorship series contain documents relating to those topics.
  - General Secretary- Treasurer, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 11)
    The General Secretary Treasurer's Office series is arranged numerically by reel number.
  - General Secretary- Treasurer and Economics Department, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 12)
    The General Secretary-Treasurer series and the Economics Department series contains documents created by the GS-T's office and the Economics Department.
    The reels of these two series are arranged numerically by reel number.
  - Affiliated Bodies and General Files, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 13)
    The Affiliated Bodies series and General Files series are arranged numerically by reel number.
    The Affiliated Bodies series and the General Files series contain documents relating to IBT locals and documents of general IBT interest.
  - Area Conferences, Staff Series, Personnel, and General Files, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 14)
    The Area Conferences series, Staff series, Personnel and General series are arranged numerically by reel number.
    The Area Conferences series, the Staff series and the Personnel series contain documents relating to the operations of the Teamsters Area conferences and to matters relatiing to IBT staff.
  - Local Unions, Agreements, Communications Department, and Safety and Health Department, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 15)
    The Local Unions series, Agreements series, Communicastions Department series and Safety and Health Departmenrt series are arranged numerically by reel number.
    These series contain correspondenece with IBT local unions, copies of agreements between locals and companies represented, and Communicationa Department and Safety and Health Department publications and correspondence.
  - State Historical Society, Wisconsin Collection, UPS, Alliance for Union Action, and JBT HQ, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 16)
    The State Historical Society of Wisconsin series, the UPS series, the Alliance for Labor Action series and the IBT HQ series are arranged numerically by reel number.
    The reels in the State Historical Society of Wisconsin series contain documents from the colelction, Records of ther IBT 1907-1952, transferred to the SHSW in the late 1960s. The UPS reels relate to UPS contracts and worker representation. The ALA reels relate to short-lived Alliance for Labor Action, an IBT and UAW joint organizing effort. The IBT HQ reels contain documents relating to the day-today operations of the Teamsters Union.
  - Miscellaneous Topics, 1953-1989; Series 1 (Box 17)
    The Miscellaneous Topics series is arranged by topic then numerically by reel number.
    This collection contains miscellaneous microfilm rolls.
- IBT History Files, 1899-1992; Series 2; 1.5 Linear Feet Box 18, 1 Record Center Box
  This series contains files having to do with International Brotherhood of Teamsters history. The files include manuscripts on Teamster history, local Teamster union history, and scanned files from the early years of the union.
  This series is arranged by subject.
  - Newspaper Clipping Biography, 1972; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters National Union German Language Constitution, 1902; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - A Brief History of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters News Service, Brief History of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1964; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dan Tobin Labor Day Speech, 1937; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - The Teamster Monitorship: A Lesson for the Future, Undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - A Brief History of the Team Drivers International Union, 1899-1903, Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - The Teamsters in Mississippi, Undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Teamsters History in Connecticut, 1992; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "The Greatest Thing I Ever Did Was Join a Union: A History of the South Dakota Teamsters during the Depression, 1988; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - A History of the Teamsters by Bernard Cook, Undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - A History of the Teamsters in Georgia, 1988; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Early News Clippings, 1906; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - The 1970 National Master Freight Agreement Research Project by Elmer Spear, 1971; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Conditions of the Chicago Teamsters Unions, 1988; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - The Teamsters in Puerto Rico, Undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - North Dakota History Vol 54 No, 2, 1987; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - IBT History Project Memorandums, 1987; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - History of Local 218 1901-1967, Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Men and Machines: A Story about Longshoring on the West Coast Waterfront, 1963; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - The Teamsters Magazine and History Vol. 3 No. 10, 1906; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Selected References/Bibliographies, Undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Teamsters in Connecticut, 1989; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - History of the Teamsters Union by Encylopedia Britannica, Undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Superior Court of Cook County Statement about the Teamsters, 1904; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Dedication of the Headquarters Building, 1955; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- IBT Locals, 1925-1977; Series 3; 3 Linear Feet Boxes 18 and 21, both record center boxes
  This series consists of files having to do with local Teamster unions.
  - Local 588, 1952-1957; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Local 377 John Angelo Testimonial Dinner, 1950; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Ammunition by Local 747 Newsletter, 1957; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Ward News, 1956-1957; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - New England Teamsters and Trucking Industry Pension Fund, 1971; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Taxicab Drivers' Union Local 156, 1947; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - What You Should Know About Your Union Local 386, Undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - An Invitation to a Better Life Local 832, 1959; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - A Guide for New Members Local 971, Undated; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Local 170, 1945-1975; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Milk Drivers Union Local 753 75th Anniversary, 1977; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Local 791 and Local 645, 1925; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Local 107 Files, 1953-1954; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Bakery, Cracker, Pie, and Yeast Wagon Drivers Union Local 734 Articles of Agreement, 1943; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Local 703, 1935; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Local 156, 1935-1946; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Local 156, 1935-1946; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Chicago Ice Wagon Drivers and Helpers Local 702 21st Anniversary Picnic Programs, 1921; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Local 464 News Clippings, 1933-1962; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Local 170 News Clippings, 1933-1962; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- IBT Newspapers, 1953-1978; Series 4; 1.5 Linear Feet Box 19, Record Center Box
  This series consists of miscellaneous newsletters by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
  - Teamsters News Service, 1962-1970; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters News Service, 1971-1977; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The International Teamster, 1953-1978; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Duplicate Copies of DRIVE Reporters, 1962; Series 4 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Biographies, 1939-1989; Series 5; 1.50 Linear Feet Box 20, Record Center Box
  This series consists of biographical information and news clippings about various Teamster leaders.
  This series is arranged by person.
  - Thomas Flynn, 1939-1944; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Thomas Flynn, 1940-1945; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Flynn, 1953-1969; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Frank Fitzsimmons, 1979-1989; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Frank Fitzsimmons and Sons, 1977-1981; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Roy Williams, 1981-1985; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Roy Williams, 1977-1981; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Dan Tobin, 1945-1950; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Dave Beck, 1977-1981; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Louis Tommer, 1950; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - John O'Brien, 1966; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Harry Tevis, 1966; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Louis Triscaro, Undated; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Gordon Conklin, 1966; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - N.W. Evans, 1906-1975; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Dominick Calabrese, 1966; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Joseph Pecora, 1977; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - W.D. Ryan, Undated; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Joey Glimco, Undated; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - D.D. Mulcahy, Undated; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Einar O. Mohn, 1966; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - John English, 1966-1969; Series 5 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- IBT Publications, 1934-1984; Series 6
  This series contains publications produced by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
  - The Teamsters Union: What Can a Truck Driver's Union Do For You, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Roster, 1977; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Teamsters Information Brochures, 1957-1958; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The Administration of Justice, 1971; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Labor Action Pamphlets, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Everything You Always Wanted to Know About DRIVE, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 21st Convention Program, 1976; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The B.A.'s Manual, 1973; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The Program Ahead Dave Beck Speech, 1952; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Report of the General Executive Board, 1941; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - A Manual of Things Worth Knowing to Better Service Your Members, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Teamster Shop Steward: His Role in Effective Leadership, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Emblem Jewelry Order Form and Information, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - National College Debate Topic, 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Fortune Magazine Articles on the Teamsters, 1941; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Proceedings of the 27th Annual National Warehouse Division Policy Committee, 1975; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - How to Write a Union Flyer, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Proceedings of the 25th Anniversary National Warehouse Division Policy Committee, 1973; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Medicare and Social Security Benefits, 1965; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Photograph Negatives and Published Materials, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - PROD Information Sheet, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - A Profile of the Teamsters Union, 1961; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Sidney Zagri Statement before the Committee on the Judiciary, 1962; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Non-Discrimination Press Release, 1958; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Personal Privacy Article, 1964; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Roy Williams Trial Press Release and Report, 1971; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Here's What You're Up Against DRIVE Film Strip, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - PROD Dispatch, 1978; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Sidney Zagri Statement Before the Committee of the Judiciary, 1962-1963; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - DRIVE 89th Congress Legislative Fact Book, 1965; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - James R. Hoffa Statement Before the Committee of the Judiciary, 1966; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Hoffa Caucus Reports, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Contract Analysis, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - DRIVE DLA Report, 1965; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Illinois Truck News Vol. 11 No. 4, 1964; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Over the Road and General Hauling Trade Division Meeting Address by James R. Hoffa, 1960; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - America on the Move News Kit, 1972; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - The Right to Work...Talking it Over, Thomas Flynn's Copy, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Status of Owner-Operators Under the Law, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Yellow Cab Company Philadelphia 21st Anniversary Program, 1942; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - National Apprenticeship Policy, 1971; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Ray Schoessling Retirement Dinner, 1984; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Pyramid Structure Graphic, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - IBT Model Test, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Conspiracy to Destroy the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Article, 1977; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Brewery Workers' Journal, 1934; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Keg and Beer Chauffeurs and Helpers Local 744 Articles of Agreement, 1977; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - What is the Teamsters Union Booklet, 1977; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - John F. English Address to the AFL-CIO, 1957; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Proposed Model Local Union Bylaws, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - The Teamsters: Corrupt Policemen of an Unruly Industry Article, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Poster: Compare Your 1977 Earnings to Your 1976 Earnings, 1978; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Teamsters Advertisements, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous Materials, Undated; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Teaching Labor Studies in the Schools Vol. II, 1988; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Organizing Manual of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1979; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Eastern Conference of Teamsters Files, 1954-1962; Series 7; 1.5 Linear Feet Box 22, 1 Record Center Box
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  This series contains publications having to do with the Eastern Conference of Teamsters.
  - Annual Reports, 1954-1958; Series 7 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Comparison of Selected Provisions, 1962; Series 7 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Testimonial Dinner of John English, 1961; Series 7 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Shop Steward's Manual, Undated; Series 7 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - A Public Relations Guide for ECT Locals, 1962; Series 7 (Box 22, Folder 61)
- FDR-Tobin Correspondence, 1933-1944; Series 8; 1.5 Linear Feet Box 23, 1 Record Center Box
  This series contains correspondence between US President Franklin Delano Roosevelt and IBT President Daniel Tobin.
  - FDR-Tobin Correspondence, 1934-1941; Series 8 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - FDR-Tobin Correspondence, 1938-1944; Series 8 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - FDR-Tobin Correspondence, 1933-1937; Series 8 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - FDR-Tobin Correspondence, 1939-1942; Series 8 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Company Files, 1949-1984; Series 9; 3 Linear Feet Boxes 24 and 25, Box Record Center Boxes
  This series is arranged by company.
  This series contains files having to do with some large companies with relationships to the Teamsters. Files include arbitration files, information files, and correspondence.
  - Sears, Roebuck, and Company, 1958; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Sears, 1959-1960; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Safeway, 1958; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Whirlpool Company, 1949-1970; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Whirlpool Corporation, 1964-1976; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Whirlpool Corporation, 1966-1975; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Whirlpool Company, 1960; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Whirlpool Corporation, 1961-1974; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Whirlpool Corporation, 1967; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Whirlpool Corporation, 1961-1967; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Wilson Athletic Company, 1964-1967; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - REA, 1964-1969; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - BRC, 1968; Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Stroh Brewery Company, 1983; Series 9 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Stroh Brewery Company, 1983-1984; Series 9 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Stroh Brewery Company, 1984; Series 9 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Stroh Brewery Company, 1976; Series 9 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Stroh Brewery Company, 1977; Series 9 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- News Clippings, 1921-1987; Series 10; 1.5 Linear Feet Box 26, 1 Record Center Box
  This series contains news clippings having to do with the Teamsters, including local IBT unions.
  - 1930's Clippings, 1931-1939; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - William Presser News Clippings, 1981; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - John Nardi News Clippings, 1977; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1970's News Clippings, 1970-1979; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1920's-1930's News Clippings, 1924-1936; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Jimmy Hoffa: Labor Leader, 1965; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Local 170 News Clippings, 1921-1938; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters Headquarters Dedication, 1955; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Local 170 Photocopied Articles, 1954; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Britannica Library Research Service Teamsters History, Undated; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Objectives of the Teamsters Article, 1971; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Detroit, Michigan News 1987 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings, 1957-1977; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Other Organization Publications, 1954-1981; Series 11; 1.5 Linear Feet Box 27, Record Center Box
  This series contains publications by organizations that are not the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Some publications are specifically related to the Teamsters. Some publications do not make specific reference to the Teamsters, but rather are relevant to the wider labor movement.
  - Labor Monographs on IBT, 1964; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Chicago and the Labor Movement: Metropolitan in the 1930's by Barbara Newell, 1961; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Trade Union Government and Collective Bargaining by Joel Seidman, Undated; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ammunition Newsletter, 1957; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Lie Detector Discredited Article, 1964; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 88th Congress Congressional Record, 1964; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Poster-size Appendix, Undated; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Report of the Comptroller General of the United States, 1981; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - IBT PROD Press Release, Undated; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Committee on the Judiciary Report on Constitutional Rights, 1965; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Alliance for Labor Action, Undated; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - How the Biggest Union Ticks, Business Week, 1955; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Peace at the Negotiating Table by Victor Riesel, 1973; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The Worker in American Fiction Annotated Bibliography, 1954; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - National Conference of Health, Welfare, and Pension Plan News, 1964; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Commonweal Vol. LXXX No. 13, 1964; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - If it Breathes, Organize it by Irwin Ross, 1970; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1991-1992; Series 11 (Box 27, Folder 18)